# <mark>VEELAM RA</mark>JINI LUGUN **UI/UX DESIGNER**

#### Contact





7349073169 <u>nilu.swt7@gmail.com</u>



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/neelam-lugun-77b0394b/



Bē https://www.behance.net/neelamlugun



https://orca-panda-h7hq.squarespace.com/config/



# Work Experience

### Marmeto | Enable commerce **UX/UI** Designer October 2022 - Present

- User research
- · Identified and troubleshoot UX problems.
- Gathered and evaluated user requirements in collaboration with
- Illustrating design ideas using user process flow. -Design user interface elements, like menus, tabs and widgets.
- · Building page navigation buttons and search fields.
- · Developed UI mock-ups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look-like.
- knowledge of UI design and technique. -Organize and Deliver rough draft proposal to internal teams and key stakeholders.
- · Conducted layout adjustments based on user feedback.
- Adhere to style standards on fonts, colors and images.
- Designed responsive design and mobile UI.
- knowledge of HTML/mobile UI.
- proficiency in photoshop and wireframing tool.
- · Up-to-date with the latest UI trends, technique and technology.

## Design projects June 2020 - January 2022

- "Littlefield" Designed and developed a mobile application for online/offline fashion and retail fashion shopping enable to drap the garment to a body shape before buy.
- "Meteor" Developed and designed a mobile application for online fashion retail shopping to guest checkout
- · Re-designed and developed Mobile application for home furnishing online shopping
- "Behealthy"Designed and developed a mobile application for health tracking and designed for messaging features and engagement activity for sharing in group of friends and family.

#### 2013-2021

#### Visual Merchandiser

Lifestyle International Pvt Ltd Forever New Apparels Pvt Ltd Bestseller Retail India Pvt Ltd

- · Provided solutions to store's specific visual and merchandising challenges using brand standards and corporate visual guidelines.
- · Designed and styled instore
- · Merchandise display.
- · Taken lead for store Marketing communication and Visual merchandiser with 5 team members in store



# Profile

Overall of 1+ years of experience in design proficiency UI/UX with process and tools with knowledge of digital marketing and marketing communication with 7+ years of experience in fashion retail. I bring rich experience in customer.



#### Education

#### Springboard UX/UI design career track

**UX/UI** methodologies & techniques 1:1 mentorship and 2 capstone projects) June 2020- January 2022

# National Institute Of Fashion Technology -Design

May 2009 - June 2013

#### Bachelor In science-B.sc

User Research

May 2006 - May 2008



0001 11000011011	3
UX writing	Problem-Solving
Persona	user interviews
User flow	Iconography
Sketching	Grids & Layout
Wireframing	Animation
Prototyping	Mobile Design
Usability Testing	Visual Design
Design Sprint	Team player
Communication skills	Team associate

Design Thinking



Miro Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop Coreldraw

**InVision** Figma